AHAMED ABDUL RAHMAN

FRONT END DEVELOPER



CONTACT





2/146, Usman Nagar, Thiyagadurgam Kallakurichi, TN -606206



SKILLS

Web Development

- HTML 5, CSS 3, BOOTSTRAP 5
- JAVASCRIPT
- GIT/GITHUB
- WordPress

Ongoing Development

- Advanced UI/UX principles
- Tools: Adobe XD, Figma
- User research & prototyping

LANGUAGES

English

Tamil

Hindi

Urdu



PROFILE

Passionate and skilled Front-End Developer with 1 Year experience in HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 5, and JavaScript. Proficient in creating responsive, user-friendly web applications and collaborating effectively using Git/GitHub for version control. Dedicated to continuous learning and development, with certifications in Web Development and UI/UX Principles to enhance user-centered design and functionality.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Lumos Technology | Front End Developer

2024- Present

- Developed responsive, mobile-first web interfaces using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and Bootstrap.
- Integrated front-end with back-end services, optimized performance, and ensured cross-browser compatibility.
- Collaborated using Git/GitHub for version control, testing, and delivering high-quality user experiences.
- Interacted directly with clients to gather project requirements, clarify bug fixes, and ensure successful project delivery.
- Created UI designs using Canva and Photoshop, and developed test cases to ensure functionality and quality.

Tech Mahindra | Associate

2023 - 2023 Dec

Worked for Qatar Visa Process handling both domestic and international customers

IndusInd Bank | VKYC Officer

2023 - 2022 Dec

Verify the customer bank details and capture signature and customer photo and do deep verification

One point one solution | CRE

2021-2022 May

Convince customer to attend webinar session about Twin Health Diabetes Reversal treatment



EDUCATION

Bachelor of Business Management

2018-2021

Vels Institute of Science, Technology and Advanced Studies Chennai

SSLC

2017-2018

AKT Academy Matric Higher Secondary School Kallakurichi

HSSC 2016- 2017

AKT Academy Matric Higher Secondary School Thiyagdurgam

